=Episode 7=
Your Highness,
Miss Xi Yuan has been abducted!
(Could it be Father's doing?)
Send men to find her at once.
Understood.
Help!
Quiet.
Keep struggling,
and I'll throw you off right now.
And then,
even a beauty like you
will be nothing but a mangled mess.
Qing Yuluo,
why did you kidnap me?
To take you to Longyuan, naturally.
Jin Yunlie cares so much about you.
That makes you very useful.
Longyuan?
Who says I'm going to Longyuan with you?
Think you can run?
Not so fast.
Who's there?
(Another expert?)
(I'm still in Huyun territory.
Better not drag this fight out.)
Shisi,
didn't we agree not to interfere?
(Finally, I've found you.)
You...
Who are you?
Shisi.
Shisi,
you never change.
How many more divine punishments
can that body of yours take?
It's an ironclad divine law
that deities must not aid mortals.
Is it worth
doing this?
Let's go.
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
It's just a normal reaction
to sudden weightlessness.
I feel better now that I've thrown up.
Oh, right,
thanks for saving me back there.
It really is you.
You're still alive.
You know me?
You don't remember me?
Sorry,
I don't think we've met.
You don't look familiar.
(She's lost her memory?)
Still,
you feel oddly familiar.
My apologies.
I must have mistaken
you for someone else.
So,
is that person very important to you?
Yeah.
You've heard
the saying:
where there's a will,
there's a way.
I hope you find her soon.
Alright.
I need to go find some food.
I'll be off now.
Thanks again!
Hey, wait up.
I'm getting a bit hungry too, actually.
Why don't we go together?
You're heading to the Huyun Capital too?
Yeah.
Let's go together then.
(Jin Yunlie must be
so worried about me.)
(I need to let him know right away
that I'm okay.)
Is it broken?
Never mind for now.
I'll deal with it
once we reach the Huyun Capital.
(I'm sorry.)
(I can't let him find you just yet.)
(I still need a little more time...)
(There's something I need to verify.)
Your Highness,
why did the Whispering Bell
respond just now,
then suddenly go silent?
Someone must have placed
a restriction
on Xi Yuan's Whispering Bell.
Should I...
No need.
The restriction can be lifted.
It just takes a little extra effort,
that's all.
Return immediately
and assist Lou Jingou
in identifying the assassin.
Tighten the patrols.
The Huyun Imperial Palace
is not open to just anyone.
Yes, Your Highness.
(Xi Yuan,)
(please be safe.)
♪Look there, upon a withered bough♪
♪A green shoot with roots in decay♪
♪If only I could stay,
quietly holding on♪
Why isn't this bell working?
I've been calling forever,
but Jin Yunlie hasn't answered.
What's this?
Braised pork buns?
Are they a Huyun specialty?
I've never had one before.
Sir, I'll take three, please.
Coming right up.
Just a moment.
Make it four.
You're treating me to just one bun?
It's only one bun,
but it's the thought that counts.
Let me go!
You brat!
Let go of me!
I'll kill you right here, you hear me?
Let go!
Please help me!
I don't want to be sold as a slave!
You don't want to?
Let go!
You owe me a lot of money, brat!
Move!
You're going on that blind date now!
Come on!
I'm not going, Mom!
You're not going?
I'm your mother!
If I say you're going, you're going!
Let her go.
Mind your own business!
Take it.
Let me go!
You won't take the hint?
Then we'll do this the hard way.
Miss.
Don't be scared.
I'm right here with you.
Your Spiritual Power is way too weak.
Weak or not, let's find out.
Go!
As long as I'm here,
no one is taking her away.
See? He's no match for me.
No one can ever sell you again.
Really?
He really won't come after me again?
Don't worry.
No one will bully you anymore,
or force you to do things
you don't want to do.
I believe you, miss.
Alright, off you go now.
Go home.
Thank you, miss.
But...
I'm sorry.
Fine.
I won't be the bad guy.
How much does that little girl owe you?
Twenty taels.
Fine.
I'll pay what she owes.
But if you ever bully her again,
I won't go easy on you.
Where's my coin pouch?
You don't even have the money,
yet you're still sticking your nose in?
Listen up,
I'm not taking a loss on this.
She owes me money. I have it in writing.
Even if you take this
to the authorities,
I'll still win.
What's the rush?
I said I'll pay you, and I will.
Your coin pouch is right here.
How did my coin pouch end up with you?
Hey,
there's the money.
Hand it over!
Here.
This isn't over.
You'll be sorry!
What happened?
You stole it?
Hey.
Get up. Talk to me.
I'm sorry, miss.
It was me. I stole your coin pouch.
My mother's illness
can't go untreated any longer.
Miss,
you both have great Spiritual Power.
Please, can you save my mother?
She's dying.
You useless fool!
Great Demon Lord,
please calm your wrath.
There was a formidable expert nearby,
far stronger than I am.
Please, Great Demon Lord,
grant me one more chance.
This time,
I'll capture her and bring her to you.
You'd better succeed.
If I can get my hands on her,
killing Jin Yunlie would be nothing.
The entire Xuanji Realm
would be mine for the taking.
We're almost there. Just up ahead.
This is my home.
♪A love letter, a passionate pursuit,
the envy of everyone♪
♪Bouquets and heartfelt confessions,
leaving me moved and fulfilled♪
♪No matter how long or hard our road,
I don't care♪
♪But you left me with this pain,
forever beyond redemption♪